<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Paul Graham Essays</title>
    <link>https://paulgraham.com/feed_paulgraham.xml</link>
    <description>Paul Graham's Essays and Writings</description>
    <atom:link href="https://paulgraham.com/feed_paulgraham.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Crazy New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/newideas.html</link>
      <description>There's one kind of opinion I'd be very afraid to express publicly.
If someone I knew to be both a domain expert and a reasonable person
proposed an idea that sounded preposterous, I'd be very reluctant
to say "That will never work."Anyone who has studied the history of ideas, and especially the
history of science, knows that's how big things start. Someone
proposes an idea that sounds crazy, most people dismiss it, then
it gradually takes over the world.Most implausible-sounding ideas are in fa...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/newideas.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fierce Nerds</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/fn.html</link>
      <description>Most people think of nerds as quiet, diffident people. In ordinary
social situations they are — as quiet and diffident as the star
quarterback would be if he found himself in the middle of a physics
symposium. And for the same reason: they are fish out of water.
But the apparent diffidence of nerds is an illusion due to the fact
that when non-nerds observe them, it's usually in ordinary social
situations. In fact some nerds are quite fierce.The fierce nerds are a small but interesting group. The...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/fn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Project of One's Own</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/own.html</link>
      <description>A few days ago, on the way home from school, my nine year old son
told me he couldn't wait to get home to write more of the story he
was working on. This made me as happy as anything I've heard him
say — not just because he was excited about his story, but because
he'd discovered this way of working. Working on a project of your
own is as different from ordinary work as skating is from walking.
It's more fun, but also much more productive.What proportion of great work has been done by people who...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/own.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Work Hard</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/hwh.html</link>
      <description>It might not seem there's much to learn about how to work hard.
Anyone who's been to school knows what it entails, even if they
chose not to do it. There are 12 year olds who work amazingly hard. And
yet when I ask if I know more about working hard now than when I
was in school, the answer is definitely yes.One thing I know is that if you want to do great things, you'll
have to work very hard. I wasn't sure of that as a kid. Schoolwork
varied in difficulty; one didn't always have to work super h...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/hwh.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird Languages</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/weird.html</link>
      <description>When people say that in their experience all programming languages
are basically equivalent, they're making a statement not about
languages but about the kind of programming they've done.99.5% of programming consists of gluing together calls to library
functions. All popular languages are equally good at this. So one
can easily spend one's whole career operating in the intersection
of popular programming languages.But the other .5% of programming is disproportionately interesting.
If you want to...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/weird.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Smart</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/smart.html</link>
      <description>If you asked people what was special about Einstein, most would say
that he was really smart. Even the ones who tried to give you a
more sophisticated-sounding answer would probably think this first.
Till a few years ago I would have given the same answer myself. But
that wasn't what was special about Einstein. What was special about
him was that he had important new ideas. Being very smart was a
necessary precondition for having those ideas, but the two are not
identical.It may seem a hair-spli...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/smart.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is There Such a Thing as Good Taste?</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/goodtaste.html</link>
      <description>(This essay is derived from a talk at the Cambridge Union.)When I was a kid, I'd have said there wasn't. My father told me so.
Some people like some things, and other people like other things,
and who's to say who's right?It seemed so obvious that there was no such thing as good taste
that it was only through indirect evidence that I realized my father
was wrong. And that's what I'm going to give you here: a proof by
reductio ad absurdum. If we start from the premise that there's no
such thing a...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/goodtaste.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting Ideas into Words</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/words.html</link>
      <description>Writing about something, even something you know well, usually shows
you that you didn't know it as well as you thought. Putting ideas
into words is a severe test. The first words you choose are usually
wrong; you have to rewrite sentences over and over  to
get them exactly right. And your ideas won't just be imprecise, but
incomplete too. Half the ideas that end up in an essay will be ones
you thought of while you were writing it. Indeed, that's why I write
them.Once you publish something, the ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/words.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heresy</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/heresy.html</link>
      <description>One of the most surprising things I've witnessed in my lifetime is
the rebirth of the concept of heresy.In his excellent biography of Newton, Richard Westfall writes about the
moment when he was elected a fellow of Trinity College:

  Supported comfortably, Newton was free to devote himself wholly
  to whatever he chose. To remain on, he had only to avoid the three
  unforgivable sins: crime, heresy, and marriage.
  [1]

The first time I read that, in the 1990s, it sounded amusingly
medieval. Ho...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/heresy.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I've Learned from Users</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/users.html</link>
      <description>I recently told applicants to Y Combinator that the best advice I
could give for getting in, per word, was 

  Explain what you've learned from users.

That tests a lot of things: whether you're paying attention to
users, how well you understand them, and even how much they need
what you're making.Afterward I asked myself the same question. What have I learned
from YC's users, the startups we've funded?The first thing that came to mind was that most startups have the
same problems. No two have e...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/users.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien Truth</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/alien.html</link>
      <description>If there were intelligent beings elsewhere in the universe, they'd
share certain truths in common with us. The truths of mathematics
would be the same, because they're true by definition. Ditto for
the truths of physics; the mass of a carbon atom would be the same
on their planet. But I think we'd share other truths with aliens
besides the truths of math and physics, and that it would be
worthwhile to think about what these might be.For example, I think we'd share the principle that a controlled...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/alien.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What You (Want to)* Want</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/want.html</link>
      <description>Since I was about 9 I've been puzzled by the apparent contradiction
between being made of matter that behaves in a predictable way, and
the feeling that I could choose to do whatever I wanted. At the
time I had a self-interested motive for exploring the question. At
that age (like most succeeding ages) I was always in trouble with
the authorities, and it seemed to me that there might possibly be
some way to get out of trouble by arguing that I wasn't responsible
for my actions. I gradually lost ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/want.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Need to Read</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/read.html</link>
      <description>In the science fiction books I read as a kid, reading had often
been replaced by some more efficient way of acquiring knowledge.
Mysterious "tapes" would load it into one's brain like a program
being loaded into a computer.That sort of thing is unlikely to happen anytime soon. Not just
because it would be hard to build a replacement for reading, but
because even if one existed, it would be insufficient. Reading about
x doesn't just teach you about x; it also teaches you how to write.
[1]Would th...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/read.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/getideas.html</link>
      <description>(Someone fed my essays into GPT to make something that could answer
questions based on them, then asked it where good ideas come from.  The
answer was ok, but not what I would have said. This is what I would have said.)The way to get new ideas is to notice anomalies: what seems strange,
or missing, or broken? You can see anomalies in everyday life (much
of standup comedy is based on this), but the best place to look for
them is at the frontiers of knowledge.Knowledge grows fractally.
From a dist...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/getideas.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Do Great Work</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/greatwork.html</link>
      <description>If you collected lists of techniques for doing great work in a lot
of different fields, what would the intersection look like? I decided
to find out by making it.Partly my goal was to create a guide that could be used by someone
working in any field. But I was also curious about the shape of the
intersection. And one thing this exercise shows is that it does
have a definite shape; it's not just a point labelled "work hard."The following recipe assumes you're very ambitious.
The first step is to ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/greatwork.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superlinear Returns</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/superlinear.html</link>
      <description>One of the most important things I didn't understand about the world
when I was a child is the degree to which the returns for performance
are superlinear.Teachers and coaches implicitly told us the returns were linear.
"You get out," I heard a thousand times, "what you put in." They
meant well, but this is rarely true. If your product is only half
as good as your competitor's, you don't get half as many customers.
You get no customers, and you go out of business.It's obviously true that the ret...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/superlinear.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Essay</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/best.html</link>
      <description>Despite its title this isn't meant to be the best essay. My goal
here is to figure out what the best essay would be like.It would be well-written, but you can write well about any topic.
What made it special would be what it was about.Obviously some topics would be better than others. It probably
wouldn't be about this year's lipstick colors. But it wouldn't be
vaporous talk about elevated themes either. A good essay has to be
surprising. It has to tell people something they don't already know.T...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/best.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start Google</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/google.html</link>
      <description>(This is a talk I gave to 14 and 15 year olds about what to do now
if they might want to start a startup later. Lots of schools think
they should tell students something about startups. This is what I
think they should tell them.)Most of you probably think that when you're released into the
so-called real world you'll eventually have to get some kind of
job. That's not true, and today I'm going to talk about a trick you
can use to avoid ever having to get a job.The trick is to start your own com...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/google.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reddits</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/reddits.html</link>
      <description>I met the Reddits before we even started Y Combinator. In fact they
were one of the reasons we started it.YC grew out of a talk I gave to the Harvard Computer Society (the
undergrad computer club) about how to start a startup. Everyone
else in the audience was probably local, but Steve and Alexis came
up on the train from the University of Virginia, where they were
seniors. Since they'd come so far I agreed to meet them for coffee.
They told me about the startup idea we'd later fund them to drop...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/reddits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Right Kind of Stubborn</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/persistence.html</link>
      <description>Successful people tend to be persistent. New ideas often don't work
at first, but they're not deterred. They keep trying and eventually
find something that does.Mere obstinacy, on the other hand, is a recipe for failure. Obstinate
people are so annoying. They won't listen. They beat their heads
against a wall and get nowhere.But is there any real difference between these two cases? Are
persistent and obstinate people actually behaving differently? Or
are they doing the same thing, and we just la...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/persistence.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder Mode</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/foundermode.html</link>
      <description>At a YC event last week Brian Chesky gave a talk that everyone who
was there will remember. Most founders I talked to afterward said
it was the best they'd ever heard. Ron Conway, for the first time
in his life, forgot to take notes. I'm not going to try to reproduce
it here. Instead I want to talk about a question it raised.The theme of Brian's talk was that the conventional wisdom about
how to run larger companies is mistaken. As Airbnb grew, well-meaning
people advised him that he had to run ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/foundermode.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When To Do What You Love</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/when.html</link>
      <description>There's some debate about whether it's a good idea to "follow your
passion." In fact the question is impossible to answer with a simple
yes or no. Sometimes you should and sometimes you shouldn't, but
the border between should and shouldn't is very complicated. The
only way to give a general answer is to trace it.When people talk about this question, there's always an implicit
"instead of." All other things being equal, why wouldn't you work
on what interests you the most? So even raising the qu...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/when.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writes and Write-Nots</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/writes.html</link>
      <description>I'm usually reluctant to make predictions about technology, but I
feel fairly confident about this one: in a couple decades there
won't be many people who can write.One of the strangest things you learn if you're a writer is how
many people have trouble writing. Doctors know how many people have
a mole they're worried about; people who are good at setting up
computers know how many people aren't; writers know how many people
need help writing.The reason so many people have trouble writing is tha...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/writes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Origins of Wokeness</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/woke.html</link>
      <description>The word "prig" isn't very common now, but if you look up
the definition, it will sound familiar. Google's isn't bad:

  A self-righteously moralistic person who behaves as if
  superior to others.

This sense of the word originated in the 18th century, and
its age is an important clue: it shows that although
wokeness is a comparatively recent phenomenon, it's an
instance of a much older one.There's a certain kind of person who's attracted to a
shallow, exacting kind of moral purity, and who dem...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/woke.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Do</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/do.html</link>
      <description>What should one do? That may seem a strange question, but it's not
meaningless or unanswerable. It's the sort of question kids ask
before they learn not to ask big questions. I only came across it
myself in the process of investigating something else. But once I
did, I thought I should at least try to answer it.So what should one do? One should help people, and take care of
the world. Those two are obvious. But is there anything else? When
I ask that, the answer that pops up is Make good new thi...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/do.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Writing</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/goodwriting.html</link>
      <description>There are two senses in which writing can be good: it can
sound good, and the ideas can be right. It can have nice,
flowing sentences, and it can draw correct conclusions
about important things. It might seem as if these two
kinds of good would be unrelated, like the speed of a car
and the color it's painted. And yet I don't think they
are. I think writing that sounds good is more likely to
be right.So here we have the most exciting kind of idea: one that
seems both preposterous and true. Let's ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/goodwriting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shape of the Essay Field</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/field.html</link>
      <description>An essay has to tell people something they don't already know. But
there are three different reasons people might not know something,
and they yield three very different kinds of essays.One reason people won't know something is if it's not important to
know. That doesn't mean it will make a bad essay. For example, you
might write a good essay about a particular model of car. Readers
would learn something from it. It would add to their picture of the
world. For a handful of readers it might even ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/field.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Lose Time and Money</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/selfindulgence.html</link>
      <description>When we sold our startup in 1998 I suddenly got a lot of money.  I
now had to think about something I hadn't had to think about before:
how not to lose it.   I knew it was possible to go from rich to
poor, just as it was possible to go from poor to rich.  But while
I'd spent a lot of the past several years studying the paths from
poor to rich, 
I knew practically nothing about the paths from rich
to poor.  Now, in order to avoid them, I had to learn where they
were.So I started to pay attention ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/selfindulgence.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having Kids</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/kids.html</link>
      <description>Before I had kids, I was afraid of having kids. Up to that point I
felt about kids the way the young Augustine felt about living
virtuously. I'd have been sad to think I'd never have children.
But did I want them now? No.If I had kids, I'd become a parent, and parents, as I'd known since
I was a kid, were uncool. They were dull and responsible and had
no fun.  And while it's not surprising that kids would believe that,
to be honest I hadn't seen much as an adult to change my mind.
Whenever I'd n...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/kids.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Do Great Work</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/greatwork.html</link>
      <description>If you collected lists of techniques for doing great work in a lot
of different fields, what would the intersection look like? I decided
to find out by making it.Partly my goal was to create a guide that could be used by someone
working in any field. But I was also curious about the shape of the
intersection. And one thing this exercise shows is that it does
have a definite shape; it's not just a point labelled "work hard."The following recipe assumes you're very ambitious.
The first step is to ...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://paulgraham.com/greatwork.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
